{"data":[{"question":"The play was very boring ________ they walked out.","a":"although","b":"so that","c":"since","d":"so","answer":"4","explain":"\n- So: used to say that someone does something because of the reason just stated.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"I couldn't unlock it ________ I had the wrong key.","a":"because","b":"so that","c":"since","d":"so","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Because + Clause: used when you are giving the reason for something.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"He agreed to go climbing ________ he hated heights.","a":"although","b":"in case","c":"since","d":"because","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Although: used to introduce a statement that makes your main statement seem surprising or unlikely.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"He got a new alarm clock ________ he'd get up on time.","a":"although","b":"so that","c":"since","d":"so","answer":"2","explain":"\n- So that: in order to make something happen, make something possible.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"He hasn't written to us ________ he left.","a":"as long as","b":"since","c":"by the time","d":"as soon as","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Since: from a particular time or event in the past until the present, or in that period of time.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"She'll only do the job ________ you pay her more.","a":"before","b":"after","c":"if","d":"while","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Conditional sentence type I: If + simple present, simple future tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"I never take an umbrella ________ it's raining heavily.","a":"when","b":"whenever","c":"if","d":"unless","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Unless: used to say that something will happen or be true if something else does not happen or is not true.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"It rained, which spoiled our picnic; but if it ________ it ________ a great success.","a":"didn't rain \/ would be","b":"had rained \/ would have been","c":"hadn't rained \/ would have been","d":"rained \/ would be","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Conditional sentence type 3: If + past perfect, would\/could\/should + have + PP.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"I live in a pleasant room ________ the garden.","a":"overlook","b":"to overlook","c":"overlooking","d":"overlooked","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Both gerund and Infinitive can be used to modify noun: \n+ Gerund: are often used when actions are real, concrete or completed.\u00a0\n+ Infinitive: are often used when actions are unreal, abstract, or future.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"I hope they ________ this road by the time we come back next summer.","a":"repaired","b":"will repair","c":"would repair","d":"will have repaired","answer":"4","explain":"\n- By the time\/when + simple future perfect\/simple present tense, simple future tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"}]}